Music
Hi everybody, hello.
I'm Sorato Okura, and I'm a comedian.
I'm Sorato Okura!
I'm Mitsusaki Koizumi.
I'm Ryoudai Nagano.
I'm Jun Muto.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes, ma'am.
What's today?
Oh!
The game we're playing today?
Yes, sir.
Cha-cha-cha-cha.
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha
Cha-o-cha-o Cha-o-cha-o
Chao Chao Chao
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
Can I just quickly explain the rules?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, sir.
What you see in front of you right now...
These are our pieces.
Pieces
Yes, sir.
There's a tube here and a dice inside.
Oh.
The dice are...
One, two, three, four...
××X, Y, and Z.
××XX
One, two, three, four.
Yes, sir.
Now, I'm going to ask you to roll the dice.
Roll the dice. I roll the dice.
And I'll look.
I'll look.
It's just me.
Just me.
I just rolled a one.
Yes.
If you were 1, go ahead.
Advance one.
Okay.
Like this
Advance the end by one.
Yes, sir.
When you see the numbers 1, 2, 3, and 4 like this...
Move forward by that number.
I see.
×You absolutely have to lie about the x's.
×Even if you get an x.
I see.
And if 1 comes up...
1, 2, 3, 4...
So, for example, if I roll a 4, it's still a 1.
You can go ahead and say "1".
So you can lie?
I can lie.
Yes, I can.
People around me...
If you think he's lying...
Call him a liar.
I see.
Yes, liar.
Okay. It's beautiful.
Yes, it's beautiful.
Yes. Say liar.
If it's really a lie...
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
I'm gonna fall off this end.
Oh.
So...
If you're lying...
I won't drop.
What? How do I fall?
Well, that's for you to decide.
How it falls off.
Oh.
But let me ask you this.
Oh, wow.
But would you mind?
Oh.
Anything's fine.
Oh, that's okay.
I've got two of my frames ahead of me.
Yes, sir.
If you can cross the edge for two, you win.
Wow.
This time, we're going to have a special rule for the local section.
Yes, sir.
If you cross, I'll cross here.
If you make it across, you win.
Yes, sir.
Applause.
Let's just... let's just do three X's.
What?
Four.
Oh, I'm scared. I'm scared.
What do I do?
Dalt!
Aah! There he goes. There he goes.
Let's play. Let's play.
I'll show you as it is.
Okay, Jen, you do the honesty thing.
Four!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Like this,
Give me a push.
Can you go ahead?
Four.
I want to go!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm a little skeptical about 4.
I'm a little skeptical with 4.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Okay, okay.
You're not very good at this.
What?
×Three.
That... x3
What?
Huh?
What? Look at his face.
I'm serious.
Who's this?
×Three.
Oh, my God.
I'm the scariest.
Can I say something?
Can I tell you?
No. Okay.
Bullshit!
Oh, my God!
Number four.
That's a "B"!
Batsu! Butt!
I still want to go.
East Village...
huh?
It's the same.
It's called a cross.
I just guessed Ryota's 3.
I just guessed Ryo-ta-san's 3 with a lie and a lie.
So that means I can go forward 3 squares, right?
Just like that...
A little cheating
Cheat
Eeeeee!
I followed the rules.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's all right
As it is.
Is it your turn?
No, it's my turn.
Oh, no.
After all...
I guessed it.
You said 3.
Four.
No way!
Wait, but you looked like you'd just made a decision.
No, just now. For a second, I thought I had it.
I was torn.
Aaaaah!
No, that was a real reaction.
1, 2, 3, 4, and Mr. Nakano
Let's move on a bit...
Huh?
Not many of them.
I guess it's my turn. I guess it's my turn then.
Here's the real reaction.
Turk boss.
I've come this far, I'm the one who's got to go.
Oh, let's go
Oh, I delivered.
Here.
I doubt that.
I'm just trying to be discreet right now.
What's this? Go, go, go!
I'm gonna be a little cautious here.
Okay?
Okay, three, go ahead.
Udder!
How about... how about... how about... how about... how about...
On three!
Aaaaah!
Oh, man, Ryoto and I are in trouble.
What are you gonna do? What are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do?
Aaaaah!
Oh, no!
This is where it gets serious.
This is so accurate.
I knew you'd suspect everything.
If they find out about the bust, we're screwed.
Oh, my God, he just cut me off.
The game is about to begin.
Here we go.
It's starting.
One.
Okay, go ahead.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're not at the finish line yet.
Oh, really?
One!
You know, the higher the number, the more suspicious I am. I knew it. The higher the number, the more suspicious I am.
I'm skeptical.
Please, please, please.
Three!
Oh, no.
That's not fair.
In the end, if you're going to answer...
I'm going to answer with a "B"!
Thank you very much.
I knew it.
He didn't say anything about a divorce.
You had this look on your face like it was the end.
All I get is a "buts.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Four.
It's like...
I'm getting a little nervous.
But what do we do with it?
We don't have to put it on 4.
No, really.
You sure?
Oh, really?
Thank you!
How'd it go?
Four!
A goal, by the way.
Oh no, you don't have to give me a 4.
But by saying that.
I was saying that, people were saying "4".
I see.
You got something good to tell me?
That's deep.
Ha!
What do you think? How's that?
Uh... uh... but... Oh, uh, but
Oh, no, no, yes, duh.
You're lying.
I just thought about it.
I've thought about it.
Now.
Two!
Oh, my God!
No way!
That sucks.
So when I get one...
Mom!
Pow!
Mom! Pooey!
I don't want to make an X if I can help it.
You're right.
This is funny.
Two.
Ah!
We're not at the finish line yet.
I know, right?
Well, but this...
No, no, no, no, no.
No, this is it.
Two.
I can't say it anymore.
Here you go.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's 2x.
Oh, I see.
Jun-kun, you're so good!
No, no, no, no, but it was the other way around.
Okay, everyone look at me.
Look at me.
I'll be right back.
4 I'm thinking... I'm thinking...
Four, dance! 4 Dance!
Woooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Yooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
We did it! Unfortunately, it's very rare.
I got it! This is the place!
Oh, no... one, two, three...
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no!
There's a line!
Oh, my God. Attack.
John's hot!
I only have three planes.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
That's pretty creepy.
All right, go ahead.
Number one.
I checked the location.
By the way, that's the bus.
It's parked.
Let's go for the night.
No, no, no, I'll let you go.
I'll let him stay the night.
You sure you don't want to do this, guys?
No, I'm just gonna start.
Wow, 10 minutes.
All right.
Two or three.
Two or three
A-ha-ha
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me think about it for a minute.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's gonna fall out.
It'll fall out!
But, Ryotan, if this is "dout" and it's OK...
If it's OK... Yes, if this is OK.
Liar.
Come on, come on.
Two.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's great.
Thank you.
No, it's here. It's here.
No, it's like a co-op game between me and Kosaku.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
We made it! We're the first ones on stage!
Yay!
There's no one left!
No, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
We're so close, Mr. Ryotan!
Mr. Ryotan, turn around!
Mr. Ryotan, turn your arm!
I wonder how he's going to take it with this.
I'm sorry, no matter what I say, it's suspicious
Two!
Two, go ahead.
What's the truth? What's the truth?
Two.
Oh, my God, I'm in a hurry.
This is so heavy.
This is so much fun.
Two.
It's okay, it's okay.
I might pull the same one in a row.
But Takato... we have to destroy him.
Who's going to take your place?
I'll tell you who. It had to be.
I was 2.
If it was two, I'd want you to go.
No, no, no. Same for me.
I'm not at the finish line yet.
I'm 2.
I'm 2, so go ahead, okay?
Okay? You're okay to go on.
All right. - All right.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Two.
Except for the batu?
No, but that's 2 for the finish line.
No, it's just barely.
It's the same.
I stopped at two.
They didn't say "down".
It was a "B".
Go, go, go, go, go.
We're in the same boat.
If Ryotan succeeds, he might be able to go to 2.
Ryotan.
No, but it was a good game.
Come on.
I won't say anything.
It was a no.
I knew it!
All right, here's the real game.
No, it's the real deal.
This is the real end.
I'll go.
Four.
I'm not gonna tell you.
I'm the one who came all this way and made you do it.I came all the way up here and made you do it, didn't I?
Of course you did.
Are you sure?
Four!
That's a four.
Four.
It's a four. It was a solid four.
It's a 4!
I don't know, man.
You're gonna have to change your technique a little bit.
What was your technique before?
Honest Face. Honest Face.
Oh, I see.
Singing face.
Now, now, now.
I don't know.
How do you feel?
Look.
You did it, didn't you?
It's nice.
Not at all.
The result is a two.
Two.
No way.
Applause.
Let's see... oh!
Oh!
Oh, okay! Maybe it's not such a good number.
- Well, I guess I'm good. - No, you've moved on.
- I came in second.
- But wait, I played ball.
- Yeah. So second place is pretty big if you advance.
- I'll take it. - I'm serious.
- No? No? Can you go?
- Can you go? - Can you go? - Can you go? - Can we go?
- I got squashed.
- I came in second. Well, I was second. - How'd you like that?
- Sure. - I'm trying to move.
- Yes, second place. - You're out!
- You're out! - Yes, I was second.
- Good job, guys!
- Oh, man, this is serious. - Good job.
- Good job. - Bye-bye.
- Oh no, now you're in my shoes. - I'm in trouble.
- Are you leaving? - Oh, it's me.
- I can't... but I don't know... his face...
- Two?
You still have the same number as me.
- Well... there's something important about this...
Well... well... if that's the case...
- Oh, my God, you guys just hang in there.
- This is a bad idea.
- It depends on the number.
- What? 4!
- I'm in trouble.
- I'm pretty sure...
- I'll fit in.
- I'll get it.
- No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- No, but this...
- No, but this... this will work, right? No, no, no, I have to tell you...
- No, no, no, I have to tell you...
- No way...
- No way... - I'm the only one who can do it.
- I'm the only one.
- You're the only one who could do it. You won!
- Well, I have no choice.
- One... two... three...
- Yeah. - Wow! Wow! Cuttin' it out!
- If Takato is the Doubt...
- If Takato is a douche... - Oh, my God, if only Takato were a douche...
- If I don't do X... - If I don't do X...
- I'm not gonna win the money... - Jun's gonna win.
- Well, I'm already so excited...
- Let's make the final before we douche.
- Let's do the final before we douche, maybe.
- Scary!
- Oh, wait, that's good.
- I want to do it before I... four... one... two... three...
- One... two... three...
- That's a double douche. But can we win?
- Both already... What? - And...
- Are you sure it's 4... Géramin?
- You can change it.
- You can change it, honestly.
- Because if you don't change it now, I'll just keep doing it if I'm out.
- Oh, my God.
- That's good. - I doubt that.
- That's suspicious.
- Three... three... three... three... three... three...
- Three, three, three, three, three, three, three, three...
- Was it three? Was it three?
- Was it three?
- Well, then, who is it?
- You don't know!
- Three... three.
- Really? - It's all over. - It's all over.
- I'm gonna win. I'm gonna win if I go on three and the next real number comes up.
- You win.
- First one's a goo, then a junkie, then a boom!
- Wow!
- Nice try!
- Nice, nice, nice edge-base thun.
- Bye-bye, everybody.
- Bye-bye.
- Oh, man.
- Wait. It's over.
- What? - How do we win? - What? - How do you win?
- What's a Dauntless Man?
- What's a "Dauntless Man"? - It's one life left.
- One life left. - That's still one strike.
- If I get four, I lose.
- I'd lose. - That's right. Three, three, four...
- Okay, I'll go with this. - Four.
- It's really a 4. - It's really a 4.
- Are you sure? - I took another swing.
- Two-sixths.
- If you get four...
- Two-sixths. - Yeah, well, two-sixths.
- I'll go with six centimeters.
- One... one...
- You're being evasive.
What do you think? What do we do with this?
- Only Joon-kun. - No, not even if Joon-kun says...
- Joon!
- Show it here! - Show us your competitive spirit!
- But, Jun, if I guess right, you win, right?
- I win. That's one. - That's right.
- But wait.
- Maybe he's just trying to make me say something.
- He's only here to make me say it. - He's here to make me say it, too.
- Wait. - No.
- No. - Hey!
- Come on.
What's the answer?
Check here.
Oh, yeah!
We won!
Congratulations!
Oh, my God.
You all got it right!
You're Chao Chao!
Chow Chow!
Chow Chow! It's Ciao Ciao!
It's Chao Chao!
It's like the Chinese constitution.
Ciao ciao!
That's great! You all got it right!
I only have two more.
Well, I've only got two.
But thanks for winning before I was gone.
Yeah, I knew it.
I was the key man.
Okay, so...
How would you have liked it if it had been Nijo Chao Chao? Gentlemen.
Ciao Ciao!
No, seriously, it was Ciao Ciao.
Yes, I didn't think about it.
It was a lot of Ciao Ciao.
It was a project filled with Ciao Ciao.
It was a project.
Chao Chao Chao.
Well, the first half was a failure.
Now that I think about it.
I thought Junko was smart.
Yes, you're right.
How was it, Junko?
My head was tired.
I don't know if it's okay to say "dat".
Or shouldn't I?
You know...
There's a fine line.
Junko was gambling at the end.
She was the last to go.
If it were me, I might have fallen.
You can see a man who's strong in the game.
What do you think?
By all means...
Please try Chao Chao Chao!
Well then, let's have our usual greetings.Well then, let's have our usual greetings.
Let's say goodbye! Ready!
Ciao!
That's a great lineup!
Hmmm...